raileurope.co.uk 2015-04-25

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement
Voyages-sncf UK Limited ("VSL") operates this Privacy Statement applying to the VSL website to
ensure it maintains visitors' rights to privacy in the online environment and to comply with data
protection and other legislation. VSL wishes to provide a secure and safe user experience and wishes
to explain how VSL will use and protect your rights to its visitors in relation to any personal data
which you may send or provide to VSL through this website.
1. Statement of Intent
From time to time, by using VSL's website you will be required to submit information about yourself
(such as name, address etc) to use services on the website or to purchase products from VSL. By
entering your details, you enable VSL and its service providers to provide you with the services and
products you select. Whenever you provide such information, VSL will treat that information in
accordance with this Privacy Statement. VSL will act in accordance with current legislation and aim
to meet current internet best practice.
2. Data Collection
VSL will only collect and use personal data voluntarily provided by visitors to this website in order for
those visitors to use VSL's services or purchase products from VSL. The data will only be used for the
purposes of the specified services or products. In doing this, VSL may gather information from your
computer (such as your IP address, browser and access times) which may be or contain personal
information. You should not disclose unrequested personal information.
3. Use of data collected
By using this website and/or providing VSL with any information you are deemed to agree to the VSL
Website Conditions of Use and the provisions of this Privacy Statement. You are also deemed to
agree to VSL using that information to send to you emails or other communications about any of
VSL's products or general news or updates, unless you notify VSL at the address given in paragraph 4
below that you wish to unsubscribe. VSL uses the data provided for the purposes of managing its
provision of services and products to you as you have requested and agreed, for administering and
managing your relationship with VSL, analysing your use of this website, updating you with special
offers, products or services and responding to your questions. Information you provide may also be
shared with other relevant travel and tourist organisations. It will be disclosed only to process
bookings and ensure your travel is completed in accordance with your ticket/pass.
4. Access to your Personal Information
You have a right to request a copy of the personal information VSL holds about you and to have any
inaccuracies corrected (we charge £10 for information requests). Please address written requests to

the Marketing Department, Voyages-sncf UK Limited, 34 Tower View, Kings Hill, West Malling, Kent,
ME19 4ED.
5. Users under 18 years
If you are under 18, please get your parent or guardians permission beforehand whenever you
provide personal information to this website.
6. Security
We will not disclose any data about you without your permission unless we are required to do so by
law and for the purposes specified above. We will take reasonable care to keep your data secure and
prevent unauthorised access to it by implementing accepted standards of technical measures and
security policies. Whilst such reasonable efforts are taken, as the internet is an open system VSL
cannot however guarantee that unauthorised third parties will never gain access to VSL's website by
overcoming VSL's precautions and security methods. VSL cannot be held liable for what
unauthorised recipients may do with information they gain access to.
7. Cookies
VSL places a "cookie" on your computer to identify when you visit the VSL website. These cookies
are used to aid and identify customer behaviour, trends and demographics. Most, if not all, websites
use cookies for this purpose. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies your computer to our servers.
Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. If you disable the
cookies you will still be able to use the website and book tickets. We reserve the right (and you are
deemed to agree) to match information gathered from cookies with any information you have given
about yourself and to use information gathered from cookies to enhance your use of our website.
Cookies are used by our suppliers and affiliates in respect of which VSL cannot advise and therefore
cannot accept any responsibility. This website may contain links to other websites and such non-VSL
websites are not governed by this Privacy Statement as VSL has no control over them. Accordingly,
VSL cannot be held responsible for the privacy and security policies and measures of other websites
you may choose to visit and you do so at your own risk. Ensure that you read and understand the
privacy and security policies of such websites so that you may understand how they collect, use and
share your information.
Voyages-sncf UK Limited
Registered office: 34 Tower View, Kings Hill, West Malling, Kent, ME19 4ED
Registered Company Number 3038075 (Incorporated in England)
VAT reg No. 673 0492 32
